

https://yuxu1.github.io/ portfolio-website/

YUFAN XU

yufanx8@gmail.com

415-746-0579

San Francisco, CA, USA (open to remote work)



SUMMARY

Certified full stack web developer with a background in business and experience in operations of a dental clinic, retail management, nonprofits office coordination, and process improvement for sales and last-mile distribution. Adaptability honed by various fast-paced environments and now excited to continuously learn while creating web applications that resolve business and user needs.

EDUCATION

Certificate in Full Stack Web

Development | CareerFoundry Jan 2024 - Aug 2024

600+ hours project-based online bootcamp

B.S. in Business | Northeastern University Sept 2015 - Dec 2018 GPA:3.8 | Magna Cum Laude

Management | Supply Chain/Operations Mgmt

SKILLS & TOOLS

Front End Web Development

- · HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript
- Frameworks/Libraries: React, Bootstrap, Angular, ¡Query, Redux, Material, Recharts
- React Native, Expo, Android Studio
- Testing: Jest, Puppeteer, Cucumber
- UX/UI (user stories, flow)

Back End Web Development

- Python & Django
- Node.js & Express
- APIs (JSON, RESTful, Postman)
- · Database (MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, SQLite3, Firebase)
- Hosting/Web Services: AWS, Google Firestore, Heroku, Netlify, Koyeb
- · QuerySet, pandas, matplotlib
- Cloudinary & WhiteNoise

Others

- Git Version Control
- Microsoft (Excel, Word, PowerPoint) Office & G-Suite
- Business (Softdent, Clicktime, Kronos)

LANGUAGES

- English
- Chinese(Cantonese, Mandarin, Taishanese)
- Korean

WORK EXPERIENCE

Assistant Manager, Office & Patient Coordinator

San Bruno Ave Dental Group

Jan 2021 - Present

- Oversee a team of 5-9 front desk members and schedules for 11 dentists and 3 hygienists to effectively meet productivity goals
- Consult and coordinate treatment with patients and insurance to ensure accurate financial calculations and treatment planning
- · Communicate with insurance, laboratories, and carriers to facilitate timely case fabrication, delivery, and claims payment

Assistant Store Manager

Sherwin Williams

Jan 2019 - Dec 2020

- Placed stock orders and merchandized storefront with the help of financial reports to effectively grow sales and minimize costs
- Coordinated staffing schedules and trained staff to promote productivity and provide an excellent customer experience
- Generated leads and built strong relationships with contractors to build a solid customer base and promote return business

Project Management & Operations Co-op

Third Sector Capital Partners

Jan 2018 - June 2018

- Fully led a firm-wide transition to a new web conferencing platform to increase user satisfaction and cut costs
- Planned and coordinated transportation logistics for the smooth execution of a firm-wide event across SF and Boston offices
- Managed office supplies inventory to promote team productivity
- Drafted new guidelines to increase team work schedule flexibility
- · Scheduled case interviews in support of recruiting efforts

Direct Store Delivery (DSD) Excellence Co-op

Bimbo Bakeries USA

Jan 2017 - May 2017

- Collected and analyzed data to identify root causes for high return routes and implemented actions to improve this metric
- Modeled sales forecasts to recommend a sales promotion plan

Retail Sales Associate

Service Systems Associates

May 2016 - Aug 2016

Leadership Assistant, Program Assistant

California Lawyers for the Arts

May 2013 - Aug 2016